Alderfer, S. Stanley Arbitration Files 5576
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Vertol Division, The Boeing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 80)
  5/24/76. Issue: Promotions.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 81)
  5/24/76. Issue: Elimination of Jobs.
- Kawecki Berylco Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2317, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 82)
  5/12/76. Issue: Sick Leave and Sick Pay.
- C.H. Masland and Sons vs. Carlisle Local, Textile Workers Union of America, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 83)
  4/21/76. Cancelled. (includes late cancellation bill)
- Confer, Smith and Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1972, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 84)
  4/23/76. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Borough of West Conshohocken vs. West Conshohocken Police, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 85)
  4/26/76. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Prestolite Battery Division, an Eltra Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6130, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 86)
  5/14/76. Issue: Suspension; Fringe Benefits.
- Pullman Trail mobile, Division of Pullman, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 347, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 87)
  5/4/76. Issue: Vacation Pay.
- Prior Coated Metals Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 8332, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 88)
  3/30/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Schulmerich Carillons, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1092, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 89)
  3/22/76. No award, just correspondence and bills.
- J.W. Rex Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5621, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 90)
  3/26/76. Issue: Overtime.
- Marty's Express, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 107, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 91)
  3/19/76. Issue: Theft; Dishonesty.
- Wood Industrial Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2964, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 92)
  2/27/76. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
- Asplundh Tree Expert Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 772, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 93)
  2/24/76. Issue: Vacation Pay.
- SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 94)
  2/6/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Polyclinic Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199P, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 95)
  1/17/76. Issue: Vacation Pay.
- Liquid Nitrogen Processing Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 8124, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 96)
  1/9/76. Issue: Discharge; Fights and Altercations.
- Stanley G. Flagg and Company, Incorporated, an ELTRA Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2326, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 97)
  2/23/76. Issue: Layoff; Seniority.
- Prestolite Battery Division, an ELTRA Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6130, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 98)
  2/4/76. Issue: Vacations; Recall.
- Philadelphia Steel and Wire Corporation vs. Upholsterers' International Union, Local 404, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 99)
  1/23/76. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Newark, Delaware, City of vs. Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 4, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 100)
  1/3/76. Issue: Merit Increases and Merit Review.
- Medical College of Pennsylvania vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199C, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 101)
  1/9/76. Issue: Cost of Living Increases.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 102)
  12/12/75. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 103)
  12/16/75. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification; Overtime.
- Firestone Plastics Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 326, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 104)
  11/28/75. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
- Wilmington, City of vs. Wilmington Fire Fighters Association, Local 1590, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 105)
  10/28/75. Issue: Retirement.
- General Battery Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5227, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 106)
  11/19/75. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems; Recall.
- Wise Foods, Division of Borden Foods, Borden, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 72, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 107)
  11/11/75. Issue: Schedules of Work; Classification of Jobs.
- Permalastic Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 15023, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 108)
  11/1/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Asplundh Tree Expert Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 772, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 109)
  12/5/75.Issue: Suspension.
- Lancaster, City of vs. Lancaster Uniformed Firemen's Association, Local 319, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 110)
  11/20/75. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Stylex, Incorporated vs. Upholsterers' International Union, Local 404, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 111)
  11/19/75. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 112)
  12/4/75. Issue: Medical Insurance.
- Schulmerich Carillons, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1092, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 113)
  10/24/75. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification; Rates of Pay.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 114)
  10/16/75. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 115)
  10/10/75. Issue: Sick Leave and Sick Pay.
- C & D Batteries, Division of Eltra Corporation vs. American Federation of Grain Millers, Local 367, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 116)
  10/11/75. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
- Birdsboro Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2348, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 117)
  11/1/75. Issue: Suspension.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 118)
  10/7/75. Issue: Seniority.
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Local 252, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 119)
  10/4/75. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
- Ogden Food Service Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 513, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 120)
  9/3/75. Issue: Seniority.
- Sinai Hospital of Baltimore, Incorporated vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199E, Division of Retail Wholesale and Department Store Employees Union, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 121)
  9/30/75. Issue: Termination of Employment.
- Peerless Steel Equipment Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1619, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 122)
  9/22/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Continental Can Company, Incorporated, Plant No. 86 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5659, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 123)
  9/17/75. Issue: Schedules of Work.
- Pennsylvania Electric Company vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 180, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 124)
  9/10/75. Issue: Contract Interpretation; Transfers.
- Wyomissing Corporation, Paper Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7146, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 125)
  7/24/75. Issue: Recall; Past Practice.
- Pretolite Battery Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6130, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 126)
  8/21/75. Issue: Suspension; Absence.
- Temple University vs Guild of Professional, Technical and Office Employees, Local 1199C, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 127)
  7/15/75. No award, only arbitrator's bill and correspondence.
- Frank M. Weaver and Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3187, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 128)
  7/21/75. Issue: Discharge.
- United States Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 1577, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 129)
  7/21/75. Issue: Absences--Discipline.
- NEAPCO Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2479, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 130)
  7/16/75. Issue: Suspension.
- J.W. Rex Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5621, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 131)
  7/8/75. Issue: Discharge.
- SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 132)
  6/4/75. Cancelled. (includes late cancellation bill)
- Classic Chemical Company vs. International Association of Machinists, District Lodge 799, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 133)
  6/12/75.
- Lukens Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1165, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 134)
  6/3/75. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Discharge.
- United States Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch No. 191, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 135)
  5/22/75. Issue: Discipline.
- Spray Products, Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 286, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 136)
  5/30/75. Issue: Suspension.
- Wilmington, Delaware, City of vs. Wilmington Fire Fighters, Local 1590, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 137)
  5/16/75. Cancelled. (includes late cancellation bill)
- Prior Coated Metals Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6527, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 138)
  5/7/75. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Warner Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3772, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 139)
  5/6/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Crown Paper Board Company, Incorporated vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 286, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 140)
  5/14/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Certain-Teed Products Corporation vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Local 103, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 141)
  4/28/75. Issue: Suspension.
- Delroyd Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6061, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 142)
  5/2/75. Issue: Overtime.
- Temple University vs. Guild of Professional, Technical and Office Employees, Local 1199C, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 143)
  4/23/75. Cancelled. (includes late cancellation bill)
- Nicholson, A Division of Cooper Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4825, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 144)
  4/22/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Kelsey-Hayes Company, Heinz Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 834, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 145)
  4/16/75. Issue: Contract Interpretation, Contracting Out.
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia vs. National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, Local 1199C, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 146)
  3/27/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 147)
  3/7/75. Issue: Discrimination.
- United States Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 157, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 148)
  2/25/75. Issue: Suspension.
- Lukens Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1165, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 149)
  1/31/75. Issue: Training and Trial Periods; Classification of Jobs.
- Lukens Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1165, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 150)
  1/25/75. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
- George Wollman, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 151)
  1/11/75. Issue: Discharge.
- Delaware State College vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 152)
  1/4/75. Issue: Contract Silence.
- Northeastern Distributing Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 429, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 153)
  12/13/74. Issue: Discharge; Discipline.
- Leeds and Northrup Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1350, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 154)
  11/30/74. Issue: Classification of Jobs. (includes correspondence)
- Lebanon, City of vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District Council 89, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 155)
  11/21/74. Issue: Arbitrability; Suspension.
- Frank M. Weaver and Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3187, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 156)
  11/5/74. Issue: Supervisors and Foremen.
- Eaton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7393, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 157)
  12/10/74. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 158)
  11/15/74. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Greater Philadelphia Movers Association, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 513, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 159)
  10/27/74. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Progressive Machine Works, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3914, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 160)
  10/31/74. Issue: Suspension.
- Sorensen Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5424, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 161)
  11/18/74. Issue: Suspension.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 162)
  10/24/74. Issue: Contracting Out.
- Hill Refrigeration Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5298, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 163)
  10/14/74. No award, only late cancellation bill and correspondence.
- Penco Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6737, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 164)
  10/18/74. Issue: Absence.
- Jones Motor, Division of Allegheny Corporation vs. Freight Drivers and Helpers, Local 557, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 165)
  10/12/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Lehigh Portland Cement Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 769, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 166)
  10/74. No award, only late cancellation bill and correspondence.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. Utility Co-Workers' Association, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 167)
  11/11/74. Issue: Vacancies.
- King Fifth Wheel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 168)
  10/16/74. No award, only late cancellation bill and correspondence.
- Cellucap Manufacturing Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 35, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 169)
  11/5/74. No award, only late cancellation bill and correspondence.
- Milk Dealers of the Scranton Area vs. General Drivers and Helpers, Local 229, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 170)
  10/74. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 171)
  9/25/74. Issue: Contracting Out.
- Griffin Pipe Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2040, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 172)
  9/74. Issue: Discharge.
- C. Schmidt and Sons, Incorporated vs. Firemen and Oilers Union, Local 473, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 173)
  9/6/74. Issue: Reduction in Force.
- Boeing Vertol Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 174)
  9/6/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 175)
  7/28/74. Issue: Lunch Periods.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 176)
  7/24/74. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- The West Company, Incorporated vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 177)
  7/24/74. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- NEAPCO Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2479, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 178)
  7/19/74. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Oakdale Printing Company vs. Graphic Arts International Union, Local 14L, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 179)
  7/10/74. No award, only arbitrator's bill and correspondence.
- Potlatch Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Ranson Local 1448, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 180)
  7/10/74. Issue: Suspension.
- Robertson-American Corporation vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Robertson Tile Local 76, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 181)
- Jones Motor, Division of Allegheny Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 384, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 182)
  6/12/74. Issue: Vacations; Vacation Pay.
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Incorporated vs. International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 183)
  6/26/74. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- Lower Bucks Cablevision, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1448, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 184)
  6/12/74. Issue: Suspension; Reinstatement.
- Metropolitan Edison Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 185)
  6/8/74. Issue: Suspension.
- Rockwell International Textile Machinery Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6996, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 186)
  6/3/74. Issue: Rules.
- Reading Aviation Service, Incorporated vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 644, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 187)
  5/17/74. Issue: Medical Insurance; Sick Pay and Sick Leave.
- AGF Wire Display Services, Incorporated vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 585, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 188)
  5/16/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Sorensen Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5424, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 189)
  5/9/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Cardwell Industries vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Alaska Local 635T, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 190)
  5/3/74. Issue: Bumping.
- Philadelphia, City of vs. APTA, District Council 47, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 191)
  4/10/74. Issue: Suspension.
- General Machine Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1890, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 192)
  3/29/74. Issue: Suspension.
- Mrs. Smith's Pie Company vs. Food Driver Salesmen, Dairy and Ice Cream Workers, Local 463, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 193)
  3/29/74. Issue: Working Conditions.
- United States Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 194)
  3/25/74. Issue: Suspension.
- John W. Moon, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1619, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 195)
  4/10/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Pennwalt Corporation, Stokes Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7055, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 196)
  3/74. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
- American Chain and Cable Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1852, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 197)
  3/22/74. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Hofman Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 198)
  3/11/74. No award, only late cancellation bill.
- Ridge Pike Lumber Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 384, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 199)
  3/11/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Strick Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 585, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 200)
  3/18/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Autocar Trucks, a division of White Motor Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 131, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 201)
  3/7/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Progressive Furniture Company vs. Upholsterers International Union, Local 37, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 202)
  2/26/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Confer Smith and Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1972, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 203)
  2/8/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Standard Steel vs. United Steelworkers of America, Locals 1940 and 2921, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 204)
  2/16/74. Issue: Cost of Living Increases.
- Armak Chemicals Division vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-398, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 205)
  2/5/74. Issue: Overtime.
- Giant Food, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 117, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 206)
  2/2/74. No award, only arbitrators bill.
- Borden Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5740, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 207)
  1/8/74. Issue: Seniority--Past Practice.
- Philadelphia, City of vs. APTA, District Council 47, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 208)
  3/1/74. Issue: Past Practice; Schedules of Work.
- Philadelphia, City of vs. District Council 47, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 209)
  12/18/73. No award, only arbitrator's bill and correspondence.
- Amstar Corporation vs. Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, Local 56, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 210)
  1/22/74. Issue: Discharge.
- Port Authority Transit Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 676, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 211)
  12/27/73. Issue: Discharge.